var title = 'Traduza para grego, sem o artigo (ο, η, το)';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "grego",
   answer: ["ελληνικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "inglês",
   answer: ["αγγλικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "francês",
   answer: ["γαλλικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "russo",
   answer: ["ρωσικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "alemão",
   answer: ["γερμανικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "espanhol",
   answer: ["ισπανικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "italiano",
   answer: ["ιταλικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "árabe",
   answer: ["αραβικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "albanês",
   answer: ["αλβανικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "português",
   answer: ["πορτογαλικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];